Preliminary Inventory of the Ohio State University, Internal Audit Records, 1897-2000 RG.6.B.2
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Accession Number UA.2000.0065, 1995-2000; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  - Circular A-133 OSU Report, 1995 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 35)
  - Circular A-133 OSURF Report, 1995 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 36)
  - OSURF Financial Report, 1995 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 37)
  - OSU Financial, 1995 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 38)
  - OSU Management Letter, 1995 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 39)
  - OSURF Management Letter, 1995 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 40)
- Accession Number UA.2000.0077, 1977-1997; 20.4 Cubic feet; (17) cartons
  Internal audit reports of various departments, colleges, centers, and offices at the main campus of OSU as well as audits of the regional campuses.
  - Project No. 0215-97019: Department of Art, 1996 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 0390-96105: Department of Zoology, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 0537-96104: English, 1996 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 0566-97056: Department of Linguistics, 1997 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 0593-97039: Department of European Language and Literature, 1996 November (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 0596-97125: Spanish and Portuguese, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 0703-96139: Human Resource Research Center, 1996 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 0707-94048: Mershon Center, 1994 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 0766-97114: Psychology, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 0777-96154: Sociology, 1996 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 0799-97050: Speech and Hearing Sciences, 1997 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 0883-97002: Agricultural Tech, 1996 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 0942-97054: Mansfield-Library, 1997 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0001, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 0942-97057: Mansfield-Maintenance and Physical Facilities, 1997 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 0942-97128: Mansfield-Student Activites, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 0971-95040: Newark, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 1100-97063: International Agriculture and Hort. Intern Program, 1997 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 1203-96004: Center on Education and Training for Employ, 1995 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 1220-95029: Department of Educational Policy and Leadership, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 1230-95030: Educational Services and Research, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 1236-95032: Educational Theory and Practice, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 1240-95032: Educational Studies, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 1265-95033: Health, Physical Education, and Recreation, 1994 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 1400-95016: Engineering Admin, 1994 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 1407-97053: Aerospace Engineering, 1997 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 1425-97139, 1997 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0002, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 1427-97141: Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1997 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 1435-95013: Computer and Information Science, 1994 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 1435-94092: Computer and Information Science, 1994 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 1470-97115: Mechanical Engineering, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 1505-97016: Consumer and Textile Science, 1996 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 2100-96048: College of Dentistry/Admin., 1995 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 2300-97007: College of Law, 1996 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 2525-96054: Internal Medicine, 1996 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 2550-97061: Pathology, 1997 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 2570-96156: Medical Biochemistry, 1996 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 2585-96103: Psychiatry, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 2925-97023: Vet Clinic Sciences, 1996 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 2976-97024: Vet Preventive Medicine, 1996 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 3000-97034: Graduate School Admin, 1996 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0003, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 4029-97001: OARNET LCI Phone Bills, 1996 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 4200-97031: Academic Affairs Admin, 1996 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 4216-97032: Admissions, 1996 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 4235-97048: University Center for International Studies, 1996 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 4238-96140: Office of International Education, 1996 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 4272-97018: UTS, 1996 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 4305-97126: Arts and Sciences Admin, 1997 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 4382-97137: Air Force Aerospace Studies, 1997 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 4384-97055: Department of Naval Science, 1997 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0004, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 4507-90037: University Registrar, 1989 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0005, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 4635-96137: Neurobiotechnology, 1996 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0005, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 4599-96096: Campus Partners, 1996 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0005, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 4710-97051: Child Care Center, 1997 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0005, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 4800-97113: University Communications, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0005, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 5020-92001: University Systems Food Facility Systems, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0005, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 5050-911110: Physical Facilities, 1991 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0005, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 5060-97143: Physical Facilities, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0006, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 5060-95017: Physical Facilities, 1994 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0006, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 5063-97058: Building and Grounds, 1997 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0006, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 5081-97052: Wexner Center Security, 1997 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0006, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 5083-970: Environmental Health and Safety, 1997 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0006, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 5092-98114: Transportation and Parking, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0006, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 5200-95015: Residence and Dining Halls, 1994 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0006, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 5449-96053: Ohio/Drake Unions, 1996 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0006, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 5477-96052: University Airport, 1995 November (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 5484-95087: Property Management, 1995 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 5502-96050: OSUE-Allen County, 1995 November (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 5502-97004: OSUE-Auglaize County, 1996 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 5502-97005: OSUE-Champaign County, 1996 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 5502-97044: OSUE-Clark County, 1996 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 5502-97006: OSUE-Coshocton County, 1996 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 5502-97027: OSUE-Delaware County, 1996 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 5502-97045: OSUE-Fayette County, 1996 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 5502-97021: OSUE-Fulton County, 1996 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 5502-97026: OSUE-Hamilton County, 1996 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 5502-97029: OSUE-Highland County, 1996 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 5502-96148: OSUE-Huron County, 1996 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 5502-97041: OSUE-Knox County, 1996 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 5502-97021: OSUE-Lawrence County, 1996 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 15)
  - Project No. 5502-97042: OSUE-Logan County, 1996 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 16)
  - Project No. 5502-97043: OSUE-Marion County, 1996 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 17)
  - Project No. 5502-97046: OSUE-Ross County, 1996 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 18)
  - Project No. 5596-97003: Piketon Research Extension Center, 1996 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 19)
  - Project No. 5597-94041: Enterprise Center for Economic Development, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 20)
  - Project No. 5608-97047: OARDC - Physical Plant, 1996 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 21)
  - Project No. 5165-92009: Reprographics, 1991 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 22)
  - Project No. 5414-95069: Athletics/Ice Rink, 1995 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 23)
  - Project No. 5502-93011: OCES-Ottawa County, 1992 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 24)
  - Project No. 5502-91120: OCES-Putnam County, 1991 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 25)
  - Project No. 5597-94041: Enterprise Center for Economic Development, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 26)
  - Project No. 0100-94016: University College of Admin, 1993 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 27)
  - Project No. 0152-94017: Continuing Education, 1993 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 28)
  - Project No. 0200-90130: College of the Arts, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 29)
  - Project No. 0215-90065: Department of the Arts, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 30)
  - Project No. 0235-90127: History of Art, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 31)
  - Project No. 0280-94019: Theatre, 1993 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0007, Folder 32)
  - Project No. 0310-93022: Biochemistry, 1992 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 0310-92025: Biochemistry, 1992 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 0310-90046: Biochemistry, 1990 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 0321-91033: Sensory Biophysics, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 0326-91034: General Biology, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 0330-90064: Entomology, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 0340-90137: Molecular Genetics, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 0390-90066: Zoology, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 0397-94021: Ohio Biological Survey, 1993 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 0502-90088: Black Studies, 1990 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 0502-92034: Black Studies, 1992 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 0505-90136: Medieval and Renaissance Studies, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 0506-94022: Women's Studies, 1993 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 0509-90094: Classics, 1990 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 0518-90133: Comparative Studies in Humanities, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 15)
  - Project No. 0527-94026: East Asian Languages and Literature, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 16)
  - Project No. 0537-90097: English, 1990 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 17)
  - Project No. 0543-90098: Foreign Language Center, 1990 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 18)
  - Project No. 0545-91035: French and Italian, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 19)
  - Project No. 0547-90140: German, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 20)
  - Project No. 0566-90045: Linguistics, 1990 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 22)
  - Project No. 0575-90139: Philosophy, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 23)
  - Project No. 0593-94003: Slavic and Eastern Language, 1993 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 24)
  - Project No. 0596-91036: Spanish and Portuguese, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 25)
  - Project No. 0614-90144: Astronomy, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 26)
  - Project No. 0614-92027: Astronomy, 1992 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 27)
  - Project No. 0642-92020: Geodetic Science, 1992 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 28)
  - Project No. 0671-94002: Mathematics, 1993 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0008, Folder 29)
  - Project No. 0694-90047: Statistics, 1990 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 0671-92019: Mathematics, 1991 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 0684-91121: Physics, 1991 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 0711-90143: anthropology, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 0722-94029: Economics, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 0733-94030: Geography, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 0744-90142: Journalism, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 0745-94031: Lantern, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 0755-94032: Political Science, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 0766-93020: Psychology, 1992 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 0777-90141: Sociology, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 0881-91069: ATI-Business Technologies, 1990 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 0883-91071: ATI-Animal Industries Tech., 1990 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 0896-91066: ATI-Student Services, 1990 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 0928-91122: Lima Campus, 1991 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 15)
  - Project No. 0971-94035: Newark Campus, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 16)
  - Project No. 0942-92016: Mansfield Campus, 1991 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0009, Folder 17)
  - Project No. 0942-92016, 1991 October (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 1014-90149: Accounting, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 1035-94036: Finance, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 1035-90096: Finance, 1990 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 1039-94037: Management and Human Resources, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 1043-94038: Management Sciences, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 1100-92022: College of Agriculture, 1992 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 1077-93305: School of Public Policy and Management, 1993 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 1107: Expenditures, 1990 (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 1123-90147: Ag Engineering, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0010, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 1127: Horticulture and Crop Science, 1986 (Box UA.2000.0077.0011, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 1178-94046: Plant Pathology, 1993 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0011, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 1200-91015: College of Education, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0011, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 1200-91112: Expenditures Book, 1991 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0011, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 1200-91112: Analytical Review, 1991 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0011, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 1200-91112: College of Education (now 1203), 1991 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0011, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 1200-90115: College of Education, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0011, Folder 7)
  - College of Education Instructional Materials Lab, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0011, Folder 8)
  - College of Education Instructional Materials Lab, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 1)
  - College of Education Instructional Materials Lab - FAS, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 2)
  - College of Education Instructional Materials Lab, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 1203-91090: CTR Education and Training, 1990 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 1203-91013: CTR on Education and Training, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 1220-9075: Educational Policy and Leadership, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 1230-90074: Educational Service and Research, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 1236-90041: Educational Theory and Practice, 1990 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 1240-90040: Educational Studies, Humanities, 1990 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0012, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 1240-91118: ERIC, 1991 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 1402-90152: Mining Engineering, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 1405-90073: Aeronautical and Astronautical Eng, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 1410-90103: School of Architecture, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 1410-93006: School of Architecture, 1992 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 1417-91017: Biomedical Engineering Center, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 1425-90083: Chemical Engineering, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 1417-92023: Biomedical Engineering Center, 1992 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 1482-90070: Natl. Regulatory Research Institute, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 1482-94057: Natl. Regulatory Research Institute, 1994 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 1501-90101: Family Relations and Human Dev., 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 1503-91019: Family Resource Management, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 1504-91020: Human Nutrition and Food Management, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 1730-90153: Family and Community Nursing, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 1750-90154: Life Span Process, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 15)
  - Project No. 2100-90042: College of Dentistry, 1990 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 16)
  - Project No. 2300-90039: Law, 1989 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 17)
  - Project No. 2503-90109: Hospital and Health Services Admin., 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 18)
  - Project No. 2504-90043: Allied Medical Professions, 1990 January (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 19)
  - Project No. 2504-92008: Allied Medical Professions, 1991 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 20)
  - Project No. 2515-92014: Medical Microbiology, 1992 March (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 21)
  - Project No. 2510-90110: Anatomy, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 22)
  - Project No. 2512-93016: Department of Emergency Medicine, 1992 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 23)
  - Project No. 2513-90111: Family Medicine, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 24)
  - Project No. 2515-90112: Medical Microbiology and Immun., 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 25)
  - Project No. 2520-93017: Medical Service Shop, 1992 December (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 26)
  - Project No. 2525-90084: Internal Medicine, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 27)
  - Project No. 2528-90156: Neurology, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 28)
  - Project No. 2535-90157: Obstertrics and Gynecology, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0013, Folder 29)
  - Project No. 2540-90158: Ophthalmology, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 2545-90085: Otolaryngology, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 2550-93018: Pathology, 1993 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 2555-90113: Pediatrics, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 2560-90159: Pharmacology, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 2565-90160: Physical Medicine, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 2570-90161: Physiological Chemistry, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 2575-90162: Physiology, 1990 May (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 2580-90086: Preventive Medicine, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 2595-90087: Surgery, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 2925-90069: Veterinary Clinical Services, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 11)
  - 2935--: Veterinary Field Service(2976), Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 2935-90068: Veterinary Field Service, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 2976-91022: Vet Preventive Medicine, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 2976--: Vet Preventive Medicine, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Information, Undated (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 16)
  - Project No. 3000-91005: Graduate School, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 17)
  - Project No. 3525-91006: Emeritus Salaries, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 18)
  - Project No. 3600-94007: Office of the President, 1993 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 19)
  - Project No. 3700-91008: Administrative Services Admin., 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 20)
  - Project No. 2927-92029: Veterinary Hospital, 1992 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 21)
  - Project No. 3900-91012: Finance Admin, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 22)
  - Project No. 3920-91040: University Budget Planning, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 23)
  - Project No. 3940-91041: Office of the Controller, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 24)
  - Project No. 3941-91042: Division of Acct., 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 25)
  - Project No. 3946-91044: Financial Training and Documentation, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 26)
  - Project No. 4001-91045: Special Purpose Research, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 27)
  - Project No. 4004-90116: Chemical Instrumentation Center, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 28)
  - Project No. 4005-90117: Central Electron Optics Fac., 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 29)
  - Project No. 4007-91045: Center for Mapping, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 30)
  - Project No. 4020-91047: Sponsored Programs Admin., 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 31)
  - Project No. 4050-91049: Byrd Polar Research Center, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 32)
  - Project No. 4050-93001: Byrd Polar Research Center, 1992 June (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 33)
  - Project No. 4100-91050: Ag Admin, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 34)
  - Project No. 4200-90118: Academic Affairs, 1990 April (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 35)
  - Project No. 4202-910151: University Honors Center, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 36)
  - Project No. 4204-91052: Young Scholars Program, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 37)
  - Project No. 4205-90067: College of the Arts and Sciences, 1990 February (Box UA.2000.0077.0014, Folder 38)
  - Project No. 4207-93007: Office of Minority Affairs, 1992 September (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 4225-91048: Academic Computing, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 4238-91025: International Students and Scholars, 1990 July (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 4250-93005: Continuing education, 1992 August (Box UA.2000.0077.0015, Folder 4)